RG 073, Department of Veterans' Affairs
Connecticut State Library
- Series 3. Administrative Files, 1886-1990
  - 1992-021 (part)
    - Fitch's Home for Soldiers and Veterans Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill), 1927-1990
      - Contracts, 1980-1984 (Box F-40)
      - National Association of State Veterans Homes, 1977-1978 (Box F-41)
      - National Association, State Director, 1981-1988 (Box F-41)
      - Mohammed Ali’s Visit (Box F-41)
      - Medical Survey, Governors Commission, 1946 (Box F-41)
      - Miner L.E. (Doctors Round Robin) (Box F-41)
      - Motion Pictures (Box F-41)
      - Monitoring Area Committee Meeting, 1987 (Box F-41)
      - Motor Vehicles, State, 1964-1979 (Box F-41)
      - National Association of State Veterans Homes, 1974-1989 (Box F-42)
      - New York, New Haven, Hartford Railroad Company, Lease (Box F-42)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1978 (Box F-43)
      - News Releases, 1977-1978 (Box F-43)
      - Nursing Home Alterations (Box F-43)
      - Nursing Recruitment, 1984-1988 (Box F-43)
      - Nursing Staff, 1949-1979 (Box F-43)
      - Officer of the Day (Box F-43)
      - Organizational/Functional Etc. Charts, 1960-1979 (Box F-43)
      - Pathologist, 1948-1978 (Box F-43)
      - Patients Accounts (Box F-43)
      - Patient Transfers, 1986-1987 (Box F-43)
        Patient information is restricted.
      - Notebook, General Orders, 1974 (Box F-44)
      - Notebook, Medicare, 1982-1984 (Box F-44)
      - Notebook, Affirmative Action, 1986 (Box F-44)
      - Patients Care Minutes, Index (Box F-45)
      - Patients Care Committee, 1954-1965 (Box F-45)
      - Patients, Transfer (Box F-45)
      - Personnel, Correspondence, 1965-1986 (Box F-45)
      - Personnel, Grievances, 1981-1983 (Box F-45)
        Patient and Personnel materials are restricted.
      - Personnel, 1970-1984 (Box F-46)
        Includes reports and pay sheets.
      - Personnel Retirements, 1960-1982 (Box F-46)
      - Pharmacy, 1940-1978 (Box F-46)
      - Pharmacy Community, 1950-1976 (Box F-46)
      - Projects List (Box F-46)
      - Public Works Projects Completed (Box F-46)
      - Public Act 77-192 (Box F-46)
      - Publicity, 1973-1979 (Box F-46)
      - Policy and Management, Office of, 1977-1978 (Box F-46)
        Personnel information restricted.
      - Press Releases (Box F-47)
      - P.M.&R. Research (Box F-47)
      - Projects, 1979-1984 (Box F-47)
      - Publicity, 1954-1974 (Box F-47)
      - Purchasing, 1947-1985 (Box F-47)
      - Rations, Distribution, Cottages, 1964-1972 (Box F-47)
      - Recapitulations (Box F-47)
      - Rehabilitation, 1956-1961 (Box F-47)
      - The Regan Report, 1973-1974 (Box F-47)
      - Reports, 1960-1967 (Box F-47)
      - Reports of Collections, 1960-1992 (Box F-48)
      - Reports of Estates, 1948-1969 (Box F-48)
      - Reports of Commander, Annual, 1955-1979 (Box F-49)
      - Reports, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1948-1959 (Box F-50)
      - Reports, Civil Defense (Box F-50)
      - Sewer System Projects, 1973-1979 (Box F-51)
      - Soldiers, Sailors and Marine Fund, 1968-1978 (Box F-52)
      - Staff Organization (Box F-52)
      - State Dinosaur Park (Box F-52)
      - Memorial Day (Box F-52)
      - Statistics (Box F-52)
      - Stockman, Roger E., Executive Officer (Box F-52)
      - Surgery, 1953-1978 (Box F-52)
      - Surveying Officers, Survey and Disposition (Box F-52)
      - Support of Dependents (Box F-52)
      - Stanber, James, M.D., Personnel Appeals Board (Box F-52)
      - Target, 1968-1988 (Box F-52)
      - Telephone, 1980-1986 (Box F-52)
      - Tissue and Transfusion Committee, 1974-1984 (Box F-52)
      - Television (Box F-52)
      - Dept. of Transportation, 1963-1979 (Box F-52)
      - Tumor Clinic (Box F-52)
      - Uniforms VHH Employees (Box F-52)
      - United Spanish War Veterans, 1960-1964 (Box F-52)
      - Special Orders, 1967-1977 (Box F-53)
      - Staff Development (Box F-53)
      - Physicians Meetings (Box F-53)
      - Surgery, 1955 (Box F-53)
      - Fund, Contributions etc., 1970-1979 (Box F-53)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission Meetings, 1984 (Box F-53)
      - Target, 1948-1987 (Box F-54)
      - United Spanish War Veterans (Maine Day Exercises) (Box F-55)
      - Utilization Review Committee, 1968-1972 (Box F-55)
      - Venereal Diseases (Box F-55)
      - Verification of Service Forms (Box F-55)
      - Veterans Administration, 1977-1989 (Box F-55)
      - Veterans Administration, 1963-1983 (Box F-56)
      - Veterans Aid, 1972-1988 (Box F-56)
      - Veterans Benefits, 1973-1986 (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Bonus (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Day, 1966-1984 (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Death, 1965-1980 (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Deaths and Claims, 1981 (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Death, 1982-1989 (Box F-57)
      - Veterans Donations and Gifts, 1973-1984 (Box F-58)
      - VFW, 1985-1986 (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital, Outdoor Pavilion (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital, Closing (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Legislation (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Mustering Out, Pay (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Pension (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Performance (Box F-58)
      - Veterans, Tax Exemption (Box F-58)
      - Veterans, Life Membership (Box F-58)
      - Veterans of Mexican Border Service (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Nursing Home, 1975 (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Organization, 1970-1982 (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Statistics, 1965-1988 (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Bonus, (Korean), 1967-1974 (Box F-58)
      - Veterans, Support of Independence (Box F-58)
      - Vietnam Veterans (Box F-58)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission (Box F-59)
        Instruction Folder and Votes by Mail.
      - Estate of Oscar Secor (Box F-59)
      - Colonel Raymond E. Gates, Commandant, 1935-1953 (Box F-59)
      - Commandants, Military Titles (Box F-59)
      - VH&HC Complaints (Box F-59)
      - Filings (Box F-59)
      - Financial Status (Box F-59)
      - Fund, Fitch's, 1979 (Box F-59)
      - Hospital Committee Meetings, 1966 (Box F-59)
      - Injunctions (Box F-59)
      - Registration, 1935 (Box F-59)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission
        Includes agendas, minutes, memorandums on votes, and other meeting material.
        See also accession 2010-001.
        - Meeting Minutes, 1935-1959 (Box F-60)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box F-61)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box F-62)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box F-63)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box F-64)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box F-65)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box F-66)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1978-1989 (Box F-67)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box F-68)
      - Vietnam Veterans, 1982-1985 (Box F-69)
      - Volunteer Services, 1958-1979 (Box F-69)
      - Volunteer Services, Monthly Reports (Box F-69)
  - 1932-001 (part)
    This box was formerly part of RG 013, Military Department. The original box number was retained.
    - Clothing requisitions, 1886-1887 (Box 174)
    - Supply vouchers, 1891 (Box 174)
    - Discharges, 1891-1895 (Box 174)
    - Disapproved applications, 1891 (Box 174)
    - Record of deaths, 1897-1923 (Box 174)
  - 2010-001
    - Veterans' Home and Hospital Commission minutes, 1980 December 17 - 1988 June 22; 4 volumes (Box 1)
      See also accession 1992-021, boxes F-60 through F-68.
      - 1980 December 17 - 1983 May 25, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1983 June 22 - 1985 March 27, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1985 April 24 - 1987 January 28, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1987 February 22 - 1988 June 22, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Board of Trustees for Department of Veterans' Affairs minutes, 1989 September 7 - 1995 April 19; 1 volume (Box 1)
      Known as Board of Trustees for the Veterans' Home and Hospital through the August 14, 1991 meeting. New name started with the September 18, 1991 meeting.
      The April 19, 1995 minutes are undated loose sheets.
    - General orders, 1954 November 15 - 1981 October 8; 1 volume (Box 1)
- Series 4. Death records (Necrological Book), 1884-1942; 1932-001 (part)
  See also Series 5, Accession 1992-021, Box 75 and Series 6, Accession 1992-031, Item 11.
  - Vol. 1, 1884-1927 (Box Item 1)
  - Vol. 2, 1927-1934 (Box Item 2)
  - 1884-1942 (Box Item 3)
    Includes list.
  - 1884-1897 (Box Item 4)
- Series 5. Historical Subject Files, 1866-1990; 1992-021 (part)
  - Fitch's Soldiers Home and Veterans Home and Hospital
    There are no boxes 76, 77, 79, 80, 83, 85
    - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission minutes, 1927-1938 (Box 73)
      - Volume 1, 1927 July 13 - 1931 May 26 (Box 73)
      - Volume 2, 1931 July 14 - 1933 May 2 (Box 73)
      - Volume 3, 1933 July 25 - 1935 February 6 (Box 73)
      - Volume 4, 1935 May 3 - 1937 April 27 (Box 73)
      - Volume 5, 1937 July 1 - 1938 October 25; 2 copies (Box 73)
    - Veterans' Home Commission Fitch's Home for Soldiers minutes, 1931 July 14 - 1933 May 2; 1 volume (Box 73)
    - Commandant’s Record, 1949-1959 (Box 74)
    - Death Records (Necrological Records), 1951-1971 (Box 75)
      - 1951-1961, 1 volume (Box 75)
        The cover is labeled 1950-1961.
      - 1961-1971, 1 volume (Box 75)
    - Veterans' Home Building Commission verbatim records, 1931-1937 (Box 78)
      See also Veterans' Home Building Commission minutes in Box 91.
      - Meetings I to IX, 1931 July - 1932 January 29; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Spine states: Vol. I.
      - Meetings X to XVIII, 1932 March 18 - 1932 November 25; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Spine states: Vol. II.
      - Meetings XIX to XXVIII, 1932 December 8 - 1935 April 15; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Spine states: Vol. III.
    - Veterans' Home Building Commission verbatim records, 1931-1937 (Box 78)
      - Meetings I to XII, 1931 July 1 - 1932 June 3; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Front cover states: Benedict M. Holden, Chairman.
      - Meetings XIII to XXVIII, 1932 June 21 - 1935 February 2; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Added to end of volume: Meeting XXIX, 1937 January 5; Meeting XXX, 1937 March 1; Termination, 1937 June 23-25.
    - Veterans' Home Commission verbatim records, 1927-1935 (Box 78)
      - Meetings I to XXIV, 1927 July 13 - 1931 March 10; 1 volume (Box 78)
      - Meetings XXVI to XLII, 1933 July 25 - 1935 February 6; 1 volume (Box 78)
      - Meetings XLIV to LVII, 1935 June 15 - 1937 April 27; 1 volume (Box 78)
        Spine states: Vol. IV.
    - Report of Commandant, Fitch's Home for the Soldiers, 1927-1934; 1 volume (Box 78)
      Spine states: Veterans Home and Hospital, Rocky Hill.
    - Photographs and audiocassettes, circa 1950-1990 (Box 81)
      Includes magnetic reel to reel tape on the 105th Anniversary, September 13, 1970.
    - Photos of Fitch's Home and aerial view of Rocky Hill Veterans' Home and Hospital, undated (Box 81)
    - "The American Soldier" Set no. 1, undated (Box 81)
    - Dewitt, J. Doyle. Lincoln in Hartford. undated. (Box 82)
      Privately printed in support of the activities of the Connecticut Civil War Centennial Commission.
    - Weld, Stanley B. Connecticut Physicians in the Civil War. Connecticut Civil War Centennial Commission., undated (Box 82)
    - Peters, Joseph P. "How Civil War Changed Hospital Care," in The Modern Hospital. 1962 May. (Box 82)
    - Wren, Jack. The Great Battles of World War I. New York: Madison Square Press, 1971. (Box 82)
    - Original lock found in Cornerstone of Fitch's Home, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1940-1990 (Box 82)
    - Photographs of staff members Vincent W. Hedges, Supervisor of Maintenance; James J. McKinnon, Jr., Director of Food Services; and Eleanor Cleary, 1940; 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Photographs of anniversary celebration, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - 100th Anniversary guest book (Box 82)
    - Photographs of opening of 125th anniversary exhibit, 1989 November 11; 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Copies of photographs from the Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Copies of Photographs from Fitch Home, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - 1940 dedication of Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Papers of the 40th Anniversary of the Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1 envelope (Box 82)
    - Report of the Soldiers Hospital Board to the Comptroller, 1888 June 30; 1 envelope (Box 82)
      Restored in 1989.
    - Correspondence of Colonel Raymond Gates regarding the properties and the transfer from Fitch's Home to the Veterans' Home and Hospital in Rocky Hill, 1940-1950 (Box 82)
    - Photographs of Colonel Raymond Gates, Commandant May 1935-January 1953, undated (Box 82)
      Contains two photographs.
    - Study of Vocational Objective Programs Approved for the Enrollment of Veterans; A Report prepared by the Veterans' Administration. Washington, D.C.: U. S. Government Printing Office, 1978 July 22 (Box 82)
    - The Fifth Infantry Division in the ETO. Prepared by The Fifth Division Historical Section, Headquarters Fifth Infantry Division, 1945. (Box 82)
    - Civil War coloring book, 1977 (Box 82)
    - Executive Committee minutes, 1908 (Box 82)
    - Hedden, James Spencer. "Colonial Wars of America: A Synopsis of the Military and Civil Records of Some of the New Haven Men Originally Buried on New Haven Green whose Grave Stones were Later Either Installed in the Crypt of Center Church or Removed to Grove Street Cemetery." 1944 January. (Box 82)
    - Mess Room Menu, 1892 (Box 84)
    - Mess Room Menu, 1893-1895; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Patient Records, 1882-1893; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Patient Records, 1887-1893; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Patient Register, 1902-1910; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Surgeon's Monthly Report, 1927 October 1; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Report of the Commandant Veterans Home and Hospital, 1935-1946; 1 volume (Box 84)
    - Connecticut Volunteers who served in the Spanish American War, 1898-1899. Published by the Adjutant General. Hartford, Conn: Hartford Press, The Case, Lockwood & Brainard Company, 1899, 2 copies (Box 86)
    - Veterans' Home Building Commission minutes, 1932 (Box 86)
    - Hartford Courant re: Old Vet at Rocky Hill, 1970; 8 copies (Box 86)
    - Discharge paper of John Connelly from Fitch's Home for Soldiers, 1888 May 31; original and copy (Box 86)
    - Executive Committee of the Soldier's Hospital Board minutes, 1908-1915; 1 envelope (Box 86)
    - Case No. 37134, W. Herbert Frost, et al. v. Benedict M. Holden, et al., Superior Court, New Haven County, 1931 December 31; original and copy (Box 86)
    - Hearing by Veterans Home Commission on charges against Captain Bennett and Sergeant Lyons, 1930 April; original and copy (Box 86)
    - Joint meeting, Veterans' Home Commission and Veterans' Home Building Commission, Lawn Club, New Haven, 1932 November 25 (Box 86)
    - Meeting of Sub Committee of the Veterans' Home Commission and the Veterans' Home Building Commission, 1932 December 2; original, 2 copies (Box 86)
    - Soldiers' Hospital Board minutes, 1902 - 1915 (Box 86)
    - "The American Soldier", undated (Box 86)
    - 125th Anniversary letter from President George H.W. Bush, 1990 June 29 (Box 86)
    - Executive Committee, Soldiers' Hospital Board minutes, 1906-1907 (Box 87)
    - Providing for Additional accommodations for Disabled and indigent Soldiers and Sailors at Fitch's Home, House Joint Resolution No. 117, 1886; copies (Box 87)
    - History and current situation at Noroton, 1888; copies (Box 87)
    - Copies of President George Bush message, 1990 June 4 (Box 87)
    - Act Concerning Aid for Widows of Veterans of Civil and Spanish-American Wars, 1921; copies (Box 87)
    - Act Concerning Aid for Widows of Veterans of Civil and Spanish-American Wars, 1887; copies (Box 87)
    - Act Authorizing Trustees of Fitch's Home for Soldiers to Transfer Property, 1887; copies (Box 87)
    - Historical Register, Connecticut State Soldiers' Home, Vol. I, 1886-1893; transcript (Box 87)
    - Report of the Soldiers Hospital Board to the Comptroller for the Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1888, copy (Box 87)
    - Soldiers' Hospital Board minutes, 1906-1909, 1915; copies, 9 folders (Box 87)
    - Duplicates (Box 88)
    - Interdepartmental memos, 1965-1970 (Box 88)
    - Clipping of transfer of patients from Noroton to Rocky Hill, 1950; copy (Box 88)
    - Clipping, Veteran and volunteer Adam Raczkowski; article on Flag Day, 1983 May - June (Box 88)
    - Exhibit (Box 88)
    - Newspaper articles; Copy of appeal by Mrs. Fitch, copies and originals (Box 88)
    - Media, 1970, 1984 (Box 88)
    - Harper's Weekly, 1866 March 17 (Box 88)
      Multiple copies of originals and reproductions.
    - Leslie's Illustrated, 1866 March 17 (Box 88)
      Multiple copies of originals and reprodctions of page 404.
    - Patient Care and Rehabilitation Committee meeting, 1959-1963 (Box 88)
    - Construction, 1959 December (Box 88)
    - Selling property in Darien (Fitch's Home), 1940-1968 (Box 88)
    - Act Providing for the Establishment of a Soldiers' Home, H.B. 14, 1963 (Box 88)
    - Pictures of the Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1940; photocopies (Box 88)
    - History of Fitch's Home, 1940 (Box 88)
    - Map showing property of the Fitch Home and Hospital for Soldiers, undated (Box 88)
    - Letter to Raymond Gates, 1930 (Box 88)
    - Incorporation papers - statutes re appropriations, etc. (Box 88)
    - Act Concerning Payment of Funeral Expenses, 1923 (Box 88)
    - Act Concerning Aid for Widows of Veterans of Civil and Spanish-American Wars, 1921 (Box 88)
    - History and current situation at Noroton, 1888 (Box 88)
    - Form for patient information, 1896; original and copy (Box 88)
    - Act Concerning Soldiers' Hospital Board, 1887 (Box 88)
    - Act Authorizing Trustees of Fitch's Home for Soldiers to Transfer Property, 1887 (Box 88)
    - Act Providing for Additional Accommodations - Fitch's Home, 1886 (Box 88)
    - Fitch's Home for Soldiers Memorial dedication, 1984 May 27 (Box 88)
    - Program dedication Veterans' Cemetery, 1985 (Box 88)
    - Information for Visitors booklet, 1979 (Box 88)
    - Report of the Committee to Study Medical and Hospital Service at the Connecticut Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1946 (Box 88)
    - Community Advisory Service Center for Connecticut Veterans pamphlet, 1946 (Box 88)
    - Insurance report, Fitch's Home for Soldiers, 1926 (Box 88)
    - Special Laws Vol. V incorporating Fitch's Home, 1932 (Box 88)
    - Senate meeting / Report legislative - sunset review, 1981 (Box 88)
    - Veterans' Insurance Act; Fact sheet Rocky Hill, 1974 (Box 88)
    - Articles on Benjamin Fitch, 1949 (Box 88)
    - New York Herald article on Veterans Home and Hospital, 1948 (Box 88)
    - Dedication Veterans' Home, 1940 September 14 (Box 88)
    - Veterans' Home and Hospital, Rocky Hill, 1932, 1940-1950 (Box 88)
    - List of employees before 1940, copies (Box 88)
    - Extracts from Connecticut Health Bulletin, 100 Anniversary, 1965 September (Box 88)
    - History, 1965 (Box 88)
    - Report Veterans' Home and Hospital, 1961 (Box 88)
    - 105th Anniversary program article with programs, 1970 (Box 88)
    - 105th Anniversary, also 30th Anniversary, 1970 (Box 88)
    - 1948 (Box 88)
    - 1949 (Box 88)
    - 1950 (Box 88)
    - Addition to the hospital, 1948; copies (Box 88)
    - Letters on funds and Fitch plan, 1945-1946 (Box 88)
    - Bill 999, 1943; copies (Box 88)
    - Construction/building/repairs, 1942-1944 (Box 88)
    - Transfer of Home to Rocky Hill, 1940 (Box 88)
    - History of Fitch's Home, 1940; copies (Box 88)
    - Naval Reserve Radio School - vault combination, 1940 (Box 88)
    - Act Concerning Making an Appropriation for the Construction and Equipment of a Soldiers' Home at Rocky Hill, 1933 (Box 88)
    - Letter to Raymond Gates and lot information for Fitch property, 1930, 1938 (Box 88)
    - Program entertainment - Fitch's Home for Solders, 1893; original and copy (Box 88)
    - Act Concerning Payment of Funeral Expenses, 1923; copies (Box 88)
    - Photograph of Gov. John Dempsey, photocopy (Box 88)
    - American Legion Post 45 and V.A. Cemetery photographs, photocopies (Box 88)
      See also accession 1992-031, box 12.
    - Shorthand letter (Box 88)
    - Post card notice of the closing of Fitch's Home for the Soldiers, 1940 (Box 88)
    - Veterans' Home Commission regulations and laws affecting Veterans, 1930-1932 (Box 88)
      Includes By-Laws.
    - Maps of Fitch's Home for the Soldiers and the city of Darien, 1949, undated (Box 88)
    - Blueprint General Assembly Act: Appropriations to build Veterans Home and Hospital in Rocky Hill, 1933; photostat (Box 88)
    - Dedication of Gates Cemetery, 1957 (Box 88)
    - 1864 Incorporating Fitch's Home for the Soldiers (Box 88)
    - An Appeal to the Patriotic Citizens of this Republic (Box 88)
    - Soldiers Hospital Board, Report of Hearing on Complaints, held at Fitch's Home for the Soldiers, 1915 November 23 (Box 88)
    - Unlabeled folder (Box 88)
    - Framed photograph, Ella Grasso and Michael Owens (Box 89)
    - Framed photograph, Alvin Smith (Box 89)
    - Framed photograph, William Wholean (Box 89)
    - Framed photograph, Arthur O’Connell (Box 89)
    - Framed photograph, Charles Sprague (Box 89)
    - F. Leslie, The Soldier in Our Civil War: A Pictorial History of the War (1861-1865), (New York: Stanley Bradley Publishing Company, 1890 ), volume I. (Box 90)
    - F. Leslie, The Soldier in Our Civil War: A Pictorial History of the War (1861-1865), (New York: Stanley Bradley Publishing Company, 1890 ), volume II. (Box 90)
    - Bill and receipt to transport inmates on railroad, 1891 June 30 (Box 91)
    - G.W. Adams, Doctors in Blue: The Medical History of the Union Army in the Civil War, (Dayton, Ohio.: Press of Morningside, 1985 ). (Box 91)
    - Medal of Honor Recipients, 1863-1973, (Washington, D.C.: United States Government Printing Office, 1973 October 22 ). (Box 91)
    - Veterans' Home Building Commission minutes, 1931 July 1 - 1937 June 25 (Box 91)
      Meetings I to XXX. Includes a copy of the law creating the Commission; Termination.
      See also Veterans' Home Building Commission verbatim records in Box 78.
    - Federal Laws Pertaining to Veterans, 1914-1950, (Washington, D.C.: United States Government Printing Office, 1951 June 11 ). (Box 91)
      Also contains a booklet titled:
      Laws Relating to Veterans and Their Dependents Enacted On and After June 27, 1950 and Through November 1, 1951, (Washington, D.C.: United States Government Printing Office, 1951 November 8 ).
    - J. Blakeney, Heroes: U.S. Marine Corps, 1861-1955, (Washington, D.C.: Gulthrie Lithograph Co., Inc., 1957 ). (Box 91)
    - Life's Picture History of World War II, (New York: Time Incorporated, 1950 ). (Box 91)
- Series 6. Miscellaneous Records, 1878-1951; 1992-031
  - Historical roster of Connecticut State Soldiers’ Home, circa 1880-1889
    - 1 - 499, 1 volume (Volume Item 1)
    - 500 - 999, 1 volume (Volume Item 2)
    - 1000 - 1499, 1 volume (Volume Item 3)
    - 1500 - 1999, 1 volume (Volume Item 4)
    - 2000 - 2499, 1 volume (Volume Item 5)
    - 2500 - 2999, 1 volume (Volume Item 6)
    - 3000 - 3499, 1 volume (Volume Item 7)
    - 3500 - 4000, 1 volume (Volume Item 8)
      The spine states 3500 - 3999.
    - 4001 - 4500, 1 volume (Volume Item 9)
  - Record of “invalid soldiers” admitted to Fitch’s Home, New Haven Hospital, and Hartford Hospital, 1878-1891; 1 volume (Volume Item 10)
  - Necrological record from Fitch’s Home for Soldiers, 1884-1951; 1 volume (Volume Item 11)
  - American Legion photos of Fitch’s Home for Soldiers, 1929; originals + photocopies (Box Box 12)
    See also box 88 for additional photocopies.
  - Leslie's Illustrated, 1866 March 17; original (Box Item 13)
  - Benjamin Fitch letter to the Trustees, 1865 October 3; original + typed copy on foam board. (Box Item 14)